one45.com 2010-01-28

# Healthcare Education Administration Software - one45

This Privacy Policy for Cytiva will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' changing needs. We may change our privacy practices from time to time. If we make any changes, this privacy statement will be updated accordingly. 

Cytiva respects your privacy when you take advantage of all the Internet offers. We're committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful, safe, online experience that you can get anywhere. 

Cytiva operates on the following privacy principles: 

We will explicitly ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you ("Personal Information"). Generally, this information is requested when you register for a particular service, ask for more information, or when applying to become a partner. 

Our site and applicable service partners use your Personal Information solely to operate our site and services and to inform you of new features, services, and products. Your Personal Information is not sold to, nor given access to, third party vendors. 

From time to time, Cytiva may also gather anonymous information to be used or shared with third parties. This information does not personally identify you but may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer. Generally this information is collected through "traffic data" and may entail the use of "Cookies", "IP addresses", or other numeric codes used to identify a computer.

Cytiva may provide links to outside resources in an effort to help you gather more business information. We are not responsible for the content provided on these sites, their privacy policies, or how they treat information about their users. The reliability, availability, legality, performance and other aspects of resources on Internet sites other than www.Cytiva.com is beyond our control, and we make no representations or warranties with respect to such sites. 

Cytiva may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Cytiva, our site or other Cytiva users, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of other stakeholders and public users. 

If at any time you believe that Cytiva has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail to [privacy@Cytiva.com](mailto:privacy@one45.com) and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.
